EDUN OLUKUNLE ELIJAH

I am a self-motivated and goal-oriented developer with experience building websites and web applications. I am adept at coming up with real solutions to satisfy client requirements. I have experience working with ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET Core REST API, Entity Framework Core, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgresSQL, Git, GitHub, and Git-Action, Docker, Kubernetes.

House no 18, Kadiri Street, Alausa, Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria, NG. +2348169688127 Email:kunle_edun@yahoo.com Github:https://github.com/gktech1

EXPERIENCE

Decagon, Lagos — Software Engineer

AUGUST 2020 - Present

- A member of a team developing and implementing backend APIs for a Water distribution Application.
- Built projects with .Net, React.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres, or NoSQL databases like MongoDB.
- Experience writing unit and integration test.
- Practice Agile methodologies.

Earlycode, Abuja — software developer

SEPTEMBER 2018-2020

- A member of a team that developed a web based ecommerce solution.
- Experience writing unit test.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres

New Horizon, Lagos — software developer

SEPTEMBER 2018-2022

- A member of a team that developed a web based ecommerce solution.
- Experience writing unit test.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres

PROJECTS

shopriseng.com:

An e-commerce application for fashion where users can browse through different fashion items, add to cart, checkout, and make purchases.

Technologies Used - C#, MySql, Sass.

Link Error! Hyperlink reference not valid.

AquaWaterPlc API:

The project Is a water distribution project, we are tasked to build an application that facilitates water

Technologies Used: .Net WebApi, Swagger, heroku, Postgres. **Link:** https://aquawaterapp.herokuapp.com/swagger/index.html

Contact API:

This project is a contact api application to manage contacts information using C-sharp, API ASP.NET Core Framework, Swagger, Heroku.

Technologies Used: Net WebApi, Swagger

Link: https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- React Hooks
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- SQLServer
- MySQL
- Postgresql
- Heroku
- Jira
- .Net mvc
- .Net web Api
- Docker
- Version Control with Git and Github.
- Test-Driven Development.

Bank Application:

This project is a window form application with login and registration, account opening, deposit, withdrawal, transfer features.

Link: https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

TODO Application:

This project is a window form application with setting up what is to be done in your daily activities. **Link:** https://contactbookappapi.herokuapp.com/swagger

EDUCATION

Moshood Abiola Polytechnic Abeokuta — HND (COMPUTER ENGINEERING)

August 2014 - FEBRUARY 2018

Higher National Diploma from Moshood Abiola Polytechnic Abeokuta, Nigeria.